Review exercise 136, description and set phrase test. Mark the intonation and then
repeat after me.
The school kids took the subway downtown for their field trip on urban living. Our
local sheriff had a bumper sticker on his back bumper. The homeowners thought they
had to pay property taxes to the federal government. There were small tremblers
after the earthquake in San Francisco.
The geology club went on a camping trip to Mount Hood.
The award ceremony at the Hilton Hotel lasted for two hours.
Bob Smith took his surfboard out on a stormy day near Diamond Head.
The Boy Scouts pitch their pup tents on the mountaintop in the pouring rain.
It's a little late to ask the babysitter to stay overnight.
The sixth graders were reading comic books and drinking chocolate milk.